之后丽芙的角色就说
And then Liv's character was like,
哦不  你可没这么干
"oh, no, you didn't!"
之后那个坏女孩就说
And then the bad girl was like,
哦是的  我就这么干了
"oh, yes, I did."
之后她们怒气冲冲的来了一场舞蹈比赛
And then they had an angry dance-off.
就像是
It was like--
亚蒂  亚蒂  亚蒂  亚蒂
Artie. artie. artie! artie!
你够了
That is enough.
下床去
Get off the bed.
好吧
Fine.
之后她们化解恩怨  成了对好朋友
And then they made up and became best friends.
好了 同志们
All right, people.
请把注意力集中到窗台上
Please direct your attention to the window seat,
你们能看到很多丽芙
Where you will find every stuffed animal
从小到大玩过的毛绒玩具
Liv has ever played with.
这些都是可供购买的
Also available for purchase.
我还要花钱买那些我送她的吗
Do I have to pay for the ones I gave her?
你只要不把从她桌子底下
I'm not answering that question
抠来的口香糖吐出来
Until you've returned the gum
我就不回答你的提问
You took from under her desk.
嘿  孩子们  你们在楼上么
Hey, boys, you up there?
老爸来了  大家快躲起来
Dad's coming. everybody hide!
我指的是躲到鞋橱里
I mean, to the shoe closet.
好了  同志们
All right, people.
起步转移  继续转移
And we're moving. and we're moving.
转移速度快点
And we're moving faster.
都赶快躲进去啊
So that means move faster.
嘿  你们俩在丽芙和玛蒂的房间里干嘛
Hey, what are you doing in Liv and maddie's room?
我们只是太想念她们了
We just miss them so much.
还有那堆阁楼里的毛绒玩具是怎么回事
And why are their stuffed animals down from the attic?
我们也太想念它们了
We missed them too.
那台垃圾粉碎机彻底坏了
Well, the garbage disposal's fried.
我要去五金店买一台新的
I have to go to the hardware store to get a new one.
果然  你确实是铁血真男儿啊
Yeah, you're a real man's man.
我先离开一会儿
I'll see you later.
对了  帮我个忙
Hey, do me a favor.
把那些毛绒玩具都放回阁楼
Put those stuffed animals back in the attic.
它们挺吓人的
They're creepy.